#### ABOUT ME

I am an experienced, selftaught and highly driven Software Engineer on a continuous learning journey who loves to learn-by-coding

Passionate about the Rust programming language, distributed systems, applied Cryptography and cuttingedge Blockchain research



Winterthur (Zürich, Switzerland)



+41 76 229 11 60



jonaspauli089@gmail.com

# SOCIALS



#### Github

@jonas089

Open source projects revolving around Cryptography, Distributed Systems and Rust



## LinkedIn

@jonas-pauli



#### Medium

@jonas\_casper

- Cryptography and zk
- Blockchain architecture
- Applications of merkle trees

# JONAS PAULI

R&D Engineer

## EXPERIENCE

## 09 / 2022 - Today

#### **R&D** Engineer

Casper Association

- Research and Development of Blockchain scaling and complex privacy solutions, leveraging "Zero Knowledge" Cryptography
- Architecture and Implementation of a Zero Knowledge Blockchain Transaction Rollup system
- Development of novel finance solutions and algorithmic standards,- proving and verifying executions with Cryptography

07 / 2022 - 09 / 2022

#### R&D Assistant

Casper Association

- Rust Smart Contract development (Blockchain application development)
- Specialization in Distributed solutions and applied Cryptography

# EDUCATION

## 05 / 2024 - 08 / 2024

Zero Knowledge Graduate Program

Rareskills

- Expert level graduate education for highly specialized Blockchain engineers
- "Conquer the fearsome Math and code Zero Knowledge algorithms from scratch"

# PROJECTS

#### Acropolis

- ETH Berlin 2024 **Hackathon** Project: Authorized, Anonymous **Voting protocol**
- Technologies used: Rust, Risc0 ZKVM
- Github @cspr-rad/acropolis

#### Kairos

- Blockchain Transaction Rollup (scaling solution), also known as a "Layer 2 zk rollup"
- Github @cspr-rad/kairos